<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<maps>
	
	<map>
		<filename>chs_glade.xml</filename>
		<name>Glade, but multiple things went wrong in Aldrheim</name>
		<description>
 Aldrheim's diversity committee decided that goblins and beastmen were way too overrepresented in this arena.
 FIREBALLS FOR ALL CREATURES yelled one of the wizards, receiving applause from everybody.
 
 However, the department for meteorology control have been in a coma for several weeks now
 after drinking "a few" too many glasses of wine... 
 Who knows what kind of chaos ensues...
		</description>
		<version date="2021-02-19" playable="true"  finished="false"/>
	</map>
	
	
	<map>
		<filename>chs_havindr_arena.xml</filename>
		<name>Diminuendo'd Wizards (Havindr Arena)</name>
		<description>
 Same waves as the hard version. 
 All players are permanently shrunk and receive the staff Grandfathers Clock. Increased speed but decreased health and resistance to all damage. 

 WIP.
		</description>
		<version date="2021-02-19" playable="true" finished="false"/>
	</map>
	
	
	<map>
		<filename>chs_mines.xml</filename>
		<name>Dehydrated Mine Workers (Cavern)</name>
		<description>
 The headmaster sent you down to mine a few precious metals but oh no! You forgot your water bottles!
 How long can you last without proper hydration in this hot underground mine?
 
 Maybe you can drink your sweat or use the sweat as water in your spells?
 
 
 And to make things worse, the goblins and trolls are very angry that the order of Magick has
 been sending down wizards to mine the precious metals.
 
 Very. angry.
		</description>
		<version date="2021-02-19" playable="true"  finished="true"/>
	</map>
	
	
	<map>
		<filename>chs_vulcanus.xml</filename>
		<name>Endless Survival Wizard Trial</name>
		<description>
 Steroids were banned by the Aldrheim Council of Fitness and Health not too long ago because numerous wizards
 exhibited grave side effects such as ripping their robes off and other aggressive behaviour.
 These days everyone takes their pre workout before an arena fight...
 but sometimes it's just too much caffeine...
 
 How long can you survive the onslaught of these hyperactive wizards?
		</description>
		<version date="2021-02-19" playable="true"  finished="false"/>
	</map>
</maps>